Finding aid for the Experiments in Art and Technology records, 1966-1993 (bulk 1966-1973)
Experiments in Art and Technology records
- Audio tapes, 1966-1993; Series VII.; ca. 8.5 lin. ft. 13 boxes
  - Pepsi Pavilion, other projects, meetings, and symposia, (Reel-to-reel tapes), 1967-1970
    - Executive meeting, #1, 1970 Sep 12-13 (Reel R93)
      1 sound tape reel (ca. 32 mins.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original. [See also C93]
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (ca. 32 min.): analog, 7 /12 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (ca. 32 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Executive meeting, #2, 1970 Sep 12-13 (Reel R94)
      1 sound tape reel (side 1: 2 hr, 5 min., side 2: 56 min., 37 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original. [See also C94]
      3 sound tape reels of 3 (3 hr., 1 min., 37 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 /12 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      3 sound discs of 3 (CDs) (3 hr., 1 min., 37 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Executive meeting, #3, 1970 Sep 12-13 (Reel R95)
      1 sound tape reel (side 1: 2 hrs., 5 min., side 2: 1 hr. 59 min., 34 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original. [See also C95]
      4 sound tape reels of 4 (4 hr., 4 min., 34 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      4 sound discs of 4 (CDs) (4 hr., 4 min., 34 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Executive meeting, #4, 1970 Sep 12-13 (Reel R96)
      1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 2 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original. [See also C96]
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (1 hr., 2 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CD) (1 hr., 2 min., 30 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Meeting for history #1 (Reel R97)
      1 sound tape reel (2 hr., 2 min.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 7 in. Original. [See also C97]
      4 sound tape reels of 4 (ca. 2 hr., 2 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      4 sound discs of 4 (CDs) (ca. 2 hr., 2 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Meeting for history #2 (Reel R98)
      1 sound tape reel (26 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original. [See also C98]
      1 sound tape reel (26 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (26 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Solomon (Reel R99)
      1 sound tape reel (31 min., 49 sec.): analog, mono.; 7/12 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "Solomon,...In my greed for fame I forgot my God..."
      1 sound tape reel (31 min., 49 sec.): analog, mono.; 7/12 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (31 min., 49 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Voices of East Harlem / Öyvind Fahlström, Den Helige Torsten Nilsson, 1993 Dec (Reel R100)
      1 sound tape reel (48 min., 38 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Side 1: no label, Side 2: "SLUTLAPP RUbrik: (enl. Protokoll) DEL 4..." Label on box: "Voices of East Harlem," and "12/93: no cassette copy made." [Note: information in title from reformatter.]
      1 sound tape reel (48 min., 38 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (48 min., 38 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Making a film (Reel R101)
      1 sound tape reel [missing].
    - Electric Raga in D, Tschudin, 1971 Nov 12-13 (Reel R102)
      1 sound tape reel (2 hr., 6 min., 4 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Written on box: "Electric Raga in D [illegible] good," and "12/93: no cassette copy made."
      3 sound tape reels of 3 (2 hr., 6 min., 4 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      3 sound discs of 3 (CDs) (2 hr., 6 min., 4 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Train to Calcutta, part 1, 1970? (Reel R103)
      1 sound tape reel (32 min.): analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "Part 1 - Train to Calcutta." Sound track for film or video? Professional quality.
      1 sound tape reel (32 min.): analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (32 min.): digital. Copy master.
    - Train to Calcutta, part 2, 1970? (Reel R104)
      1 sound tape reel (27 min., 30 sec.): analog; 71/2 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "Part II - Train to Calcutta." Sound track for film or video? Professional quality.
      1 sound tape reel (27 min., 30 sec.): analog; 71/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
    - Continuous train, 1970? (Reel R105)
      1 sound tape reel (16 min., 30 sec.): analog; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel and box: "Continuous train." Tape sounds as though it consists of copied portions of tapes R103 and R104.
      1 sound tape reel (16 min., 30 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (16 min., 30 sec.): digital. Copy master.
    - Chandralekha, 1970? (Reel R106)
      1 sound tape reel (20 min. 30 sec.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "Chandra copy...."
      1 sound tape reel (20 min., 30 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (20 min., 30 sec.): digital. Copy master.
    - Ahmedabad birds, 1970? (Reel R107)
      1 sound tape reel (1 hr.): analog, mono.; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel and box: "Ahmedabad birds..."
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (1 hr.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (1 hr.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Ahmedabad, 1970 Nov (Reel R108)
      1 sound tape reel (54 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel and box: "Ahmedabad...Nov. 1970." Includes 1 p. typed letter from National Institute of Design in Ahmedabad, Inda, with 1 p. list of tape contents.
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (54 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (54 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - New York Collection for Stockholm: George Segal talking about Marcel Duchamp's "Etant Donné" (Reel R109)
      1 sound tape reel: analog. Original. [missing]
      Made into a record for New York Collection for Stockholm Portfolio. [Reel-to-reel tape is missing, i.e. not received from E.A.T.; see Box 79 for phonograph record.]
    - Öyvind Fahlström, sounds for his film, Kisses Sweeter Than Wine, 1966 (Reel R145)
      1 sound tape reel (49 min., 39 sec.): analog, mono.; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Labels on box: "EAT ART Öyvind Fahlström Collage tape with Swedish, English material from films, radio, plays, etc. Ref # 145." "DAT: 14/9 - 66.Ö.F.Film - New York." [See also C145]
      1 sound tape reel (49 min., 39 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (49 min., 39 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
  - Klüver talks and lecture-demonstration Series, (Reel-to-reel tapes), ca. 1967-1968
    - Klüver talk, "Interface: Artists/Engineers," presented at MIT, 1967 Apr 21 (Reel R146)
      1 sound tape reel (4 min.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      1 sound tape reel (4 min.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (4 min.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Klüver talk, Toronto, 1968 (Reel R147)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "Klüver talk at Toronto 1968, 147." Labels on reel: "Klüver #3 / Rub affairs" and "MASTER." [See also C147-C149]
    - Klüver talk, Toronto, dub for Sherman #1, 1968 (Reel R148)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Label on reel: "Klüver #1: dub for Sherman / no. 1693." Label on box: "Klüver dub for Sherman Toton 1968 #1." [See also C147-C149]
    - Klüver talk, Toronto, (Dub #2 for Sherman), 1968 (Reel R149)
      1 sound tape reel (32 min., 45 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 in. Original.
      Label on box: "Klüver for Sherman Toronto 1968." Written on box: "Toronto 1968 BK [illegible] sounds systems, Good." [See also C147-C149]
      1 sound tape reel (32 min., 45 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (32 min., 45 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Klüver talk at color convention, undated (Reel R150)
      1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 7 min., 45 sec.): analog, mono.; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original.
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (1 hr., 7 min., 45 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sounds discs of 2 (CDs) (1 hr., 7 min., 45 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Ken Knowlton, 1968 (Reel R159)
      Transcribed 1968 Apr 14.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Dr. Seymour Papert, Computer Language, Apr 1 [1968?] (Reel R160)
      1 sound tape reel (2 hr., 2 min., 59 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Written on box: "Property E.A.T. Dr. Seymour Papert, April 1st Computer Language."
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (2 hr., 2 min., 59 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (2 hr., 2 min., 59 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Dr. J.W. Sellers, Dissolving papers, lecture, 1968 Feb 26 (Reel R161)
      Transcribed 1968 Mar 28. Label on box: Dr. J.W. Sellers, Dissolving Papers." and "Dr. Sellers, Property E.A.T., Tape of lecture given 2-26-68."
      4 sound tape reels of 4: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7in. Archival master.
    - Stan Vanderbeek talk, 1968? (Reel R162)
      1 sound tape reel (2 hr., 18 min.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      "Transcribed Mar 12. Duplicate."
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (2 hr., 18 min.): analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (2 hr., 18 min.): digital. Copy master.
    - Frank Winslow, Plastics #1 of 2, 1968 Feb 11 (Reel R163)
      1 sound tape reel (65 min., 21 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Written on box: "2-11-68 Frank Winslow - Plastics #1 of 2 Transcribed - E.A.T. - 3/4/68." Label on box: "S. Winslow - 1."
      1 sound tape reel (65 min., 21 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (65 min., 21 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Frank Winslow, Plastics #2, 1968 Feb 11 (Reel R164)
      Label on box: "2-11-68, Frank Winslow, Plastics #2 of 2, Transcribed E.A.T. 3-5-68, Completed 3/6." Label on box spine: "S. Winslow - 2." [See also R163]
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master. 2 reels??
    - Martha Turi #1, 1968? (Reel R165)
      Transcribed 1968 Mar 19. Label on box: "165, #1 Martha Turi." Tape also includes voice of Rudy Marshall, producer of acrylics.
    - Norman Nelson, Union Camp Co., 1968 Feb 27 (Reel R166)
      1 sound tape reel (72 min., 36 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 7 in. Original
      Written on box: "Property of E.A.T. 1 of 1 Norman Nelson Union Comp. Co. - given 2-27 Transcribed 4-2-68 Sent to Speaker."
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (72 min., 36 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (72 min., 36 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Dr. P. Bruins #1, Plastics-casting, molding and controls, held at Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1968 Feb 15 (Reel R167)
      Label on box: "Property of E.A.T., #1 of 2, plastics, Dr. P. Bruins..."
    - Dr. Bruins, Plastics-casting, molding and controls, held at Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, #2 of 2, 1968 Feb 15 (Reel R168)
      1 sound tape reel (44 min., 13 sec.): analog, mono.; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original.
      1 sound tape reel (44 min., 13 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (44 min., 13 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Herbert Bonhert (IBM), Computer poetry, [1968?] Mar 31 (Reel R169)
    - Ron Baeker, 1968? (Reel R170)
      Labels on box: "Baeker" and "Ron Baecker, 1 1/2." Baeker shows a film for 12 min. and soundtrack can be heard in the distance.
      4 sound tape reels of 4: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival masters.
    - Leon Harmon, Computer generated images, 1968 Mar 3 (Reel R171)
      1 sound tape reel (107 min., 22 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Written on box: "Transcribed - 4.9.68 Property E.A.T. Leon Harmon - still images sent to speaker published."
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (107 min., 22 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (107 min., 22 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Lou Kellem, TV Equipment and Capabilities, [1968] Feb 18 (Reel R172)
      1 sound tape reel (61 min., 13 sec.): analog, mono.; 3 3/4 ips, 7 in. Original.
      Written on box: "Lou Kellem T.V. Equipment + Capabilities 2-18 Transcribed Property Experiments in Art and Technology 3-29."
      1 sound tape reel (61 min., 13 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (61 min., 13 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Bennett talk, undated (Reel R173)
      1 sound tape reel (83 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 5 in. Original.
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (83 min., 30 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (83 min., 30 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Evans talk, undated (Reel R174)
      1 sound tape reel (81 min., 42 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 5 in. Original.
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (81 min., 42 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (81 min., 42 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Benson, 1968? (Reel R175)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 5 in. Original.
    - Seeley #1, 1968? (Reel R176)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 5 in. Original.
    - Letvin #1, undated (Reel R177)
      1 sound tape reel: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Archival master.
    - Seeley #2, 1968? (Reel R177a)
    - Towndorf, 1968? (Reel R178)
      3 sound tape reels of 3: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CD): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - Harris, 1968? (Reel R179)
    - Hunter, 1986? (Reel R180)
    - Letvin #1, 1968? (Reel R181)
      1 sound tape reel: analog. Original.
      Not reformatted. [See R177?]
    - Letvin #2, 1968? (Reel R182)
      2 sound tape reels of 2: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Archival master.
    - Robert Anderson, 1968? (Reel R183)
      3 sound tape reels of 3: analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Archival master.
    - R. Feller, 1968? (Reel R184)
    - Kogelnik, 1968? (Reel R185)
  - Klüver talks and lecture-demonstration series (Reel-to-reel tapes), ca. 1966-1971
    - John Krauskopf talk #1, undated (Reel R186)
      1 sound tape reel (65 min., 55 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 5 in. Original.
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (65 min., 55 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (65 min., 55 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - John Krauskopf talk #2, undated (Reel R187)
      1 sound tape reel (62 min., 36 sec.): analog, mono.; 1 7/8 ips, 5 in. Original.
      1 sound tape reel (62 min., 36 sec.): analog, mono.; 7 1/2 ips, 5 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (62 min., 36 sec.): digital, mono. Copy master.
    - E.A.T. meeting / E.A.T. history, 1966 Nov 30 (Reel R188)
      1 sound tape reel (111 min., 28 sec.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      2 sound tape reels of 2 (111 min., 28 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (111 min., 28 sec.): digital. Copy master.
    - E.A.T. history / Unidentified talk on acrylics, undated (Reel RU01)
      1 sound tape reel (45 min., 55 sec.): analog; 7 in. Original.
      Track 1: Narration about EAT with music (11:52); Track 2: Unidentified talk on acrylics (34:03). Original tape unnumbered.
      1 sound tape reel (45 min., 55 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips, 7 in. Archival master.
      1 sound disc (CD) (45 min., 55 sec.): digital. Copy master.
  - Sound cassettes, ca. 1967-1971
    Cassettes are original recordings and copies of the 7 in. reel-to-reel recordings. Cassettes were numbered by E.A.T., and some cassettes hold multiple recordings. Tapes record materials relating to 9 Evenings, Pepsi Pavilion, other projects, meetings, lectures, symposia.
    Reformatted versions are described below the originals, but are shelved separately.
    - 9 Evenings
      - Alfons Schilling, Hay and Whitman interviews (Cassette C1 & C6)
        1 sound cassette of 1. Original.
        Side A: Alex Hay interview with Alfons Schilling [See also R6]. Side B: Schilling and Whitman interview on telephone [See also R1].
        3 sound tape reels of 3: analog; 7 /12 ips. Archival master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (CDs): digital. Copy master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (CDs): digital. Use copy.
      - Material for Schilling film on 9 Evenings (Cassette C2-C4)
        1 sound cassette: analog. Original.
        Side A: Schilling JSNE3 and JSEN2 [See also R4, R3]. Side B: Schilling JSNE1 [See also R2].
        2 sound tape reels of 2: analog; 7/12 ips. Archival master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (CDs): digital. Copy master
      - Material for Schilling film on 9 Evenings and R. Whitman (Cassette C5 & C29)
        Side A: Whitman: 2 holes of water [See also R29]. Side B: Interviews / Schilling sound [See also R5].
        3 sound tape reels of 3: analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
      - Alex Hay; Lucinda Childs (Cassette C7 & C30)
        Side A: Lucinda Childs sound [See also R30]. Side B: Alex Hay performance (C7; see R7)..
      - Interview with Steve Paxton,; Greta Garbo, Debbie Drake, 15 Nov 1971 n.d (Cassette C8 & C9)
        Side A: no label, Side B: no label. On insert: EAT Paxton Sound Loop tapes Ref 8 and 9 [See also R8 and R9]
        4 sound tape reels of 4: analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
      - Steve Paxton sound from 9 evenings, undated, 1966 Sep 8 (Cassette C10 & C13)
        Side A: Paxton Strange Wills [See also R10]. Side B: Stop smoking, Isometrics, John Glenn [See also R13].
      - Steve Paxton 9 evenings loop tapes (Cassette C12)
        Side A: Paxton 9 evenings loop tapes. Side B: Loop tapes cont. [See below cassette tape and R12].
      - Fahlström 9 evenings (Cassette C12 & C20-C22)
        Side A: Fahlström #12 tape cont. [C12, cont.; see above cassette and R12]. Side B: Shanghai, Fine and You, Brando [See also R20, R21, R22].
      - David Tudor "Bandoneon," Fahlström interview two years later (#16), shortsound 15-16 and loop tapes (Cassette C15? & C16?)
      - David Tudor "Bandoneon" and John Cage: Variations VII, part III (#37) (Cassette C15 & C37)
        Side A: Tudor - Bandoneon! [See also R15??]. Side B: Cage Variations VII Part III.
        2 sound tape reels of 2: analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
      - Voice of American French Service on 9 Evenings, with Fahlström interview (French) (Cassette C17)
        Side A: EAT VOA French Service 9 Eves, Side B: no label [See also R17]
        1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
        1 sound disc (CD): digital. Use copy.
      - Fahlström short piece of speech, 1 of 2 (Cassette C23-1)
        Side A: EAT 9E Fahlström speech 1 7/8 to 3 3/4 to cassette Ref 23, Side B: no label [See also R23.]
        1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 /12 ips. Archival master.
      - Fahlström speech, 2 of 2 (Cassette C23-2)
        Side A: EAT 9E Fahlström speech Sanyo copy Ref 23, Side B: no label. [See also cassette C23-1 above, and R23.] Typed on insert: EAT 9E Fahlström speech Ref #23 3 3/4 cassette recorded on Sanyo transcriber at slowest speed.
      - Schilling interview with Öyvind Fahlström and Yvonne Rainer, undated (Cassette C26a-1)
        Side A: EAT Schilling w/ Rainer + Fahlström, Side B: Schilling w/ Rainer + Fahlström [Side B is blank]. Typed on insert: EAT Schilling Interview with Yvonne Rainer and Öyvind Fahlström REf #26a.
      - Interview with Öyvind Fahlström and Robert Breer, 1967 Mar 3 (Cassette C26a-2)
        Side A: EAT 9E Interview w O. Fahlström and Robert Breer 3/3/67, Side B: EAT 9E Interview w O. Fahlström and Robert Breer 3/3/67. Typed on insert: EAT 9E Inerview with Öyvind Fahlström and Robert Breer 3/3/67 Ref #26a.
      - Interview with Bob Whitman by Simone Forti and R. Whitman interview fragments, 1966 Mar 27 undated (Cassette C27 & C28)
        1 sound cassette (ca. 77 min., 19 sec.): analog. Original.
        Side A: EAD S. Whitman Interview Fragments [See also R27]. Side B: EAT Simone Whitman Int w R. Whitman [See also R28]. Paper insert: "EAT Simone [Forti] Whitman Interview with Robert Whitman 3/27/66 REf # 27 9 Evenings 1/1" and "EAT Simone Whitman Interview Fragments with various people including Robert Rauschenberg, Ref #28 9 Evenings 1/1."
        2 sound discs of 2 (C27: 44 min., 19 sec.; C28: 33 min.)(CDs): digital. Copy master [C27, C28].
        2 sound discs of 2 (C27: 44 min., 19 sec.; C28: 33 min.)(CDs): digital. Use copy [C27, C28].
      - Lucinda Child's first performance, 1970? (Cassette C31)
        1 sound cassette (ca. 40 min., 5 sec.): analog. Original.
        Side A: EAT L. Childs sound - 1st perf. Side B: EAT L. Childs cont. Paper insert: "EAT Lucinda Childs sound from 1st performance 9 Evenings Ref # 31." [See also R31].
        3 sound reels of 3 (ca. 40 min., 5 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (ca. 40 min., 5 sec.) (CDs): digital. Copy master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (ca. 40 min., 5 sec.) (CDs): digital. Use copy.
      - Deborah Hay/Toshi piece; 18 Names Rauschenberg's opening scene (Cassette C14 & C32)
        Side A: EAT Deborah Hay / Toshi piece [C14?; see also R14?], Side B: EAT Rauschenberg 18 names [see also R32 which does not completely correspond]. Paper insert: "EAT Deborah Hay/Toshi piece Rauschenberg 18 names #32.. .Toshi Ichiyanagi 'Funakakushi' for Deborah Hay piece 9 Eves Conversation in Japanese B: 18 names from tape for Rauschenberg Open Score #32."
        2 sound tape reels of 2 (C14: 20 min., 8 sec.; C32 Side B: 1 min., 50 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (C14: 20 min., 8 sec.; C32 Side B: 1 min., 50 sec.) (CDs): digital. Copy master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (C14: 20 min., 8 sec.; C32 Side B: 1 min., 50 sec.) (CDs): digital. Use copy.
      - John Cage, 1966 Oct 16 (Cassette C33 & C34)
        1 sound cassette (ca. 83 min., 11 sec.): analog. Original.
        Side A: EAT Cage 1st performance, Side B: EAT Cage Two Mikes...." Paper insert: "EAT 9E A: Cage 1st night's performance Ref 34 B: Cage - Two mikes 40 feet apart in balcony of Armory original Ref # 33."
        3 sound tape reels of 3 (ca. 83 min., 11 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (C33 Side B: 48 min., 55 sec.; C34 Side A: 34 min. 16 sec.) (CDs): digital. Copy master.
      - John Cage Variation VII, part I and part II (Cassette C35 & C36)
        1 sound cassette (ca. 68 min., 11 sec.): analog. Original.
        Side A: EAT Cage Variations VII, Part I (C35), Side B: EAT Cage Variations VII, Part II (C36).
        2 sound tape reels of 2 (ca. 68 min., 11 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (C35: 33 min., 53 sec.; C36: 34 min., 18 sec.) (CDs): digital. Copy master.
      - Robbie Robinson interview, 1966 Sep 14 (Cassette C38)
        1 sound cassette (ca. 56 min., 37 sec.): analog. Original.
        Side A: S. Whitman Int. Robinson 1/1, Side B: R. Robinson Int. cont. 1/1. Paper insert: "EAT 9E Simone Whitman Interview with Robbie Robinson 9/16/66 Ref #38 9 Evenings 1/1." [See also R37]
        3 sound tape reels of 3 (ca. 56 min., 37 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (ca. 56 min., 37 sec.): digital. Copy master.
        2 sound discs of 2 (CDs) (ca. 56 min., 37 sec.): digital. Use copy.
      - Harriet DeLong interviews about 9 Evenings
        - Colonel Lutz; Alfons Schilling, undated (Cassette C39)
          1 sound cassette (3 min., 58 sec.): analog. Original.